Farhan Tanmoy

76-01 97th Ave. Ozone Park, NY 11416 (718) 666-7458 tanmoyfarhant5@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

Extensive experience in business management, marketing and finances, which allowed a growth mindset. This skill set has allowed companies to thrive and make a high volume of profit. Willing to take on a bigger role in a company to achieve even higher profits.

EDUCATION

Hunter College - CUNY

August 2018- Present

Majoring in Computer Science and Minoring in Accounting

SKILLS

Technical

- Proficient in object-oriented programming using
 C++ and Python
- Database management and manipulation using Microsoft Excel, VBA, and Pandas
- Proficient in photo editing and enhancing utilizing the Adobe Creative Cloud ecosystem
- Proficient in Website Development using Squarespace

Communication

- Able to speak and read in Bengali
- Customer Service and Telemarketing
- Proficient in technical writing

EXPERIENCE

Khan's Tutorial, Jamaica - Executive Administrator/Creative Director

April 2018 - PRESENT

- Executive Administrator:
 - Using various software, including word processing, spreadsheets, databases, and presentation software.
 - Reading and analyzing incoming memos, submissions, and distributing them as needed.
 - Performing office duties that include managing a records database.
 - Provide general administrative support.
- Creative Director:
 - Manage the creative process from concept to completion
 - Translate marketing objectives into clear creative strategies
 - Work closely with multidisciplinary project teams, particularly IT
 - Lead and direct the creative team in the production of all marketing collateral
 - Ensure visual communication and brand standards are met

FREELANCE

Freelance Photography - Facebook / Instragram

March 2016 - Present

• Work with clients to create concepts and marketing deliverables